Brendan Kenny

401 Valley Glen Dr. • Morrisville, NC 27560 Cell: (315)403-4642 • E-Mail: Kennbp31@gmail.com

Summary

Driven and motivated professional with a diverse skill set gained from 7 years of experience as a software support technician and 3 years of experience as a high school teacher

Relevant Skills and Software

Proficient coding with SQL • Cross Team Communications

Actively learning C, C#,

Python, HTML, and JS

Call Center Experience

Strong Troubleshooter

Empathetic and Supportive

- Documentation Management
- Authoring User Guides
- Creating Knowledge Base
- Customer Training
- QA/Product Testing

- Webinar Presentations
- Account Management
- Client Ticketing Systems
- Microsoft Office
- Adobe Photoshop
- Remote Environments

Education

2019: East Carolina University • NC Teacher Licensure • 4.0 GPA 2008: State University of New York at Oneonta • Bachelor of Arts in Music Business

Professional Work Experience

2017-Present: Social Studies Teacher - Hillside High School, Durham NC

- **Team Lead:** American History 1 and for the 2019/2020 school year.
- Excellence in working in an environment that demands extensive multi-tasking and issue prioritization.
- Three years teaching in a high poverty/urban school district with measurable growth and success.
- Classroom manager, focusing on the strengths of all students and fostering powerful relationships based on mutual respect and responsibility.

2015 - 2017: Software Support Analyst / Business Consultant-Farragut Systems, Durham NC

- Triaging, assigning, and prioritizing all incoming tickets to support staff.
- Holding weekly meetings with clients to ensure needs are met and high NPS scores are communicated.
- Ensuring SLA deadlines are met appropriately for all tickets
- Working strategically to reduce support ticket backlog
- Ensuring that solutions are appropriately documented working to **build a strong knowledge base**.
- Leading daily team meetings identifying successes, challenges, and priorities.
- Single point of contact for new client implementations and onboarding.
- Solving complex issues for users, utilizing skills and knowledge of other team members as necessary.
- Proficient with Microsoft SQL, authoring complex scripts to offer business solutions and data repair as needed.
- Adult education specialist making frequent visits to train our clients across the state.
- Documentation Management and authoring training materials
- **Lead lecturer** at client conferences, teaching better business practices and encouraging active discussion between large groups of users from different offices.
- Property Tax **Business Consultant**, performing analysis of property tax collection practices, identifying areas of improvement, and offering action plans to increase county collection rates.
- Experience with the **QA** ensuring stable releases

2010 - 2015: Technical Support / Large Accounts Manager - Syrasoft LLC, Baldwinsville NY

- Troubleshoot client issues and concerns remotely in a call center environment
- Use of **SQL** and **Microsoft Access** to troubleshoot and repair database issues.
- Use of **Visual Studio** to create and maintain custom installers for Large Accounts.
- Daily Use of **Microsoft CRM** to manage client needs and information.
- **Train customers** on the daily operation of software.
- Coordinate software releases and act as the single point of contact for our large accounts
- **QA** and testing each release prior to distribution

Achievements

- Promotion: Large Accounts Manager, Syrasoft LLC
- Award: Recognized as the Beginner Teacher of the Month during both the 2017/18 and 2018/19 school year